

CONNOR CHENG

PERSONAL INFORMATION

- Male, 29 years old
- Resides in Taipei City, Taiwan

SUMMARY

5 years of work experience, which includes software development and maintenance in the field of image recognition, as well as machine vision inspection. Also skilled in UI development using WPF and MFC, and have proficiency in programming languages including C++ and C#.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Data System Imaging Co., LTD, Taipei, Taiwan Software Engineer, 2022/07 -Present

- Job Skills: MFC, C++, Visual C++
- Responsible for image recognition software development and maintenance, my main tasks included:
 - Secondary development and algorithm development using Euresys and Cognex (CVL).
 - Optimization of existing algorithms and fixing interface bugs during the maintenance process.
 - Development of MFC for interface design, algorithm development, and integration with peripheral devices.
 - Interfacing with PLC, cameras, and lasers for peripheral device integration.
 - Evaluating the detectability of objects and performing further calculations and sorting based on specific information obtained through image tools.
- Involved developing and maintaining image recognition software, optimizing algorithms, and integrating with peripheral devices such as PLCs, cameras, and lasers.
- Development and maintenance of image recognition software
- Main tools used: Euresys, Cognex (CVL)
- Maintenance of existing image recognition software
- Development of new detection algorithms

Maxtech International Corp., Taipei, Taiwan Software Engineer, 2021/01 - 2022/06 (1 year 6 months)



- Job Skills: Automated equipment design, C#, LabVIEW, C++ Job
- Using OpenCV to implement visual inspection functionalities required for the machines and how to communicate with cameras using C#. This role allowed me to understand that machines are no longer limited to IO control and servo control.
- familiar with LabVIEW and learned how to communicate with other devices such as cameras and PLCs using LabVIEW.
- Designing automated machine equipment, software development using C#, LabVIEW, and C++

Yuanhong Automation Ltd

Software Engineer, 2019/10 - 2020/07 (10 months)

- Skills: C#, software programming
- PC-based software development
- Writing machine action sequences using Beckhoff and data exchange with Beckhoff through C#
- UI design and PC-based development. For UI design, primarily used C# WPF. As for
 PC-based development, worked with Beckhoff systems. Involved in designing a
 spring machine. The machine was connected to a Beckhoff IPC through a Panel PC,
 and commands were sent to the IPC using a window application (WPF). Examples of
 commands included specifying the distance for servo motors to travel and
 automating the production process.

Ruhyih Ltd

Assistant Engineer, 2018/01 - 2019/08 (1 year 8 months)

- · Machine circuit design and machine wiring planning
- Circuit design using EPLAN
- Creating Bill of Materials (BOM)
- Machine wiring planning and configuration

EDUCATION

Kun Shan University, 2016

B.S. in Computer and Commutation